A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Francis H. Smith to [?] 1891 Nov. 5, ALS (Box 27)
- Albert S. Hunt to Francis H. Smith 1891 Nov. 9, ALS (Box 27)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Miles 1891 Nov. 25, ALS (Box 27)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1891, 26 ALS, 1 TLS, 1 TL (fragment) (Box 27)
- Francis H. Smith to Gessner Harrison Smith (his son) 1892 Jan. 4, ALS (Box 27)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Gessner Harrison Smith 1892 Jan. 9 & 19, 2 ALS (Box 27)
- William M. Thornton to C. W. Kent 1892 Jan. 12, Telegram (Box 27)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1892 Jan.-June, 8 ALS, 1 ANS (Box 27)
- John B. Minor to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1892 Feb. 20, ALS (Box 27)
- M. Schele DeVere to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1892 Feb. 22, ALS (Box 27)
- John A. Broadus to Mary Stuart Smith 1892 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 27)
- Letters to Professor F. H. Smith 1892 Feb. 27-Dec. 16, 4 ALS (Box 27)
- Letters of condolence to Francis H. Smith 1892 Feb.-April, 15 ALS (Box 27)
- R. H. Danbey to C. W. Kent 1892 March 8, ALS (Box 27)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Fielding Miles 1892 March 12-Dec. 14, 3 ALS (Box 27)
- Mary S. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Fielding Miles 1892 March 16-May 7, 3 ALS (Box 27)
- Henry Howell Lewis to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1892 March 23, ALS (Box 27)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith 1892 March 27 & Sept. 10, 2 ALS (Box 27)
- F. H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. C. W. Kent 1892 March 29, ALS (Box 27)
- Margaret J. Preston to Mary Stuart Smith 1892 March-Sept., 2 ALS, 2 TLS (Box 27)
- John L. William to Francis H. Smith 1892 April 9-Oct. 22, 4 ALS, 2 APCS (Box 27)
- W. Gordon McCabe to C. W. Kent 1892 May 24, ALS (Box 27)
- James O. Moss to Francis H. Smith 1892 July 19, ALS (Box 27)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1892 July-Dec., 21 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 27)
- Rev. John A. Broadus to Professor Francis H. Smith 1892 Sept. 15, ALS (Box 27)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1892 Sept. 22; Oct. 3 & Dec. 5, 4 TLS (Box 27)
- James Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1892 Oct. 4 & 13, 1 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 27)
- James Lowndes to C. W. Kent 1892 Oct. 17, 1 TLS (Box 27)
- W. C. Dabney to C. W. Kent 1892 Oct. 18, 1 ALS (Box 27)
- Hunter Pendleton to C. W. Kent 1892 Oct. 30, 1 ALS (Box 27)
- Mrs. E. B. Smith to F. H. Smith, (brother) 1892 [Dec. 25], 1 ALS (Box 27)
- Letters to Francis H. Smith 1892, 2 ALS, 2 TLS (Box 27)
- James D. Jones to C. W. Kent 1893 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 28)
- E. Rosalie Thornton to C. W. Kent 1893 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 28)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1893 Jan.-June, 24 ALS, 1 Telegram (Box 28)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1893 Feb. 7, 1 TLS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1893 Fe. 23-Aug. 5, 3 ALS (Box 28)
- John Randolph Tucker to Mary Stuart Smith 1893 March 14, 1 ALS (Box 28)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1893 April 18, 1 TLS (Box 28)
- Lavinia Harwood to Mary Stuart Smith 1893 April 23, 1 ALS (Box 28)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1893 April 28-Nov. 16, 3 ALS (Box 28)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1893 May 17-Aug. 2, 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 28)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1893 May 17, 1 TLS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1893 May 22-July 13, 5 ALS (Box 28)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1893 June 29, 1 TLS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1893 June 9-Aug. 6, 6 ALS (Box 28)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1893 July-Dec., 15 ALS, 3 TLS (Box 28)
- John B. Minor to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1893 Aug. 7, ALS (Box 28)
- F. H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Fielding Miles - later Mrs. C. W. Kent 1893 Aug. 1, ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1893 Aug. 8-Sept. 17, 4 ALS, 1 ANS (Box 28)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1893 Aug. 8-Sept. 17, ALS (Box 28)
- Charles W. Kent to Mrs. Smith 1893 Sept. 4, ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to C. W. Kent 1893 Sept. 14, ALS (Box 28)
- [?] to [Charles W. Kent] [1893 Sept. ?], AL (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1893 Oct. 4-Dec. 25, 4 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 28)
- Louise Manly to C. W. Kent 1893 Oct. 24 & Nov. 1, 2 ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1893 Nov. 17 & 18, 2 ALS (Box 28)
- Charles Washington Coleman to cousin, [Mary Stuart Smith] 1893 Dec. 1, ALS (Box 28)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to mother, Eliza L. C. Harrison 1893 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 28)
- W. Gordon McCabe to C. W. Kent 1893, 4 ALS (Box 28)
- Lucy [Smith?] to Francis H. Smith 1894 Jan. 11, ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, George Tucker Smith 1894 Jan. 12-March 13, 6 ALS (Box 28)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1894 Jan.-June, 64 ALS, 2 TLS, 2 APCS, 1 printed invitation (Box 28)
- Louise Manly, John M. Manly to C. W. Kent 1894 Feb.-May, 5 ALS (Box 28)
- Bennett Windue to Charles W. Kent 1894 March 15, ALS (Box 28)
- James Lowndes to Robert M. Kent 1894 March 16, TLS (Box 28)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1894 April 9-Dec. 25, 6 ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1895 April 9-June 18, 6 ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1894 May 9-Aug. 24, 4 ALS (Box 28)
- Thomas Nelson Page to Charles W. Kent 1894 May 10, ALS (Box 28)
- H. T. Kent to C. W. Kent 1894 May 22, ALS (Box 28)
- Woodrow Wilson to Professor Charles W. Kent 1894 May 29, TLS (Box 28)
- John B. Minor to Charles W. Kent 1894 June 4, ALS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, George Tucker Smith 1894 June 25-July 30, 6 ALS (Box 28)
- James L. Corbitt to Francis H. Smith 1894 June 25, ALS (Box 28)
- T. L. Patterson to Professor F. H. Smith 1894 July 16, ALS (Box 28)
- Rosalie Smith to George Tucker Smith 1894 July 16, ALS (Box 28)
- Correspondence of Charles W. Kent 1894 July-Dec., 44 ALS, 2 APCS (Box 28)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1894 Aug. 12-Sept. 2, 4 ALS (Box 29)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1894 Aug. 14-27, 3 ALS (Box 29)
- John J. Tiger to Mary Stuart Smith 1894 Aug. 24, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1894 Aug. 29-Sept. 10, 3 ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1894 Sept. 12-Oct. 13, 3 ALS (Box 29)
- John L. William to Francis H. Smith 1894 [Sept. 12], ALS (Box 29)
- [?] to Visitors of Miller Manual Labor School 1894 Oct. 1, TL (Box 29)
- Margaret J. Preston to Mary Stuart Smith 1894 Oct. 5, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1894 Oct. 22-Dec. 30, 5 ALS (Box 29)
- E. Nevins to Charles W. Kent 1894 Dec. 13, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart [Harrison] Smith to daughter, Lelia M. Smith (Mrs. Lucian Cocke) 1894 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 29)
- E. Nevins to Charles W. Kent 1894 Dec. 17 & 26, 2 ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to C. W. Kent 1894 Dec. 27, ALS (Box 29)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1894, 14 ALS, 1 AL, 1 TLS (Box 29)
- E. Nevins to Charles W. Kent 1895 Jan. 3, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Rosalie Smith 1895 Jan. 3, APCS (Box 29)
- John B. Minor to Charles W. Kent 1895 Jan. 15, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Dr. George Tucker Smith 1895 Jan. 28-July 30, 6 ALS (Box 29)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1895 Jan.-June, 21 ALS, 2 ANS, 2 TLS, 2 TL (Box 29)
- M. Schele DeVere to Charles W. Kent 1895 Feb. 7, ALS (Box 29)
- Thomas Nelson Page to Charles W. Kent 1895 April 8, ALS (Box 29)
- George Tucker Harrison to sister, Mrs. Mary Stuart Harrison 1895 April 20, 4 ALS (Box 29)
- Robert L. Harrison to Charles W. Kent 1895 April 20, ALS (Box 29)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to sister, Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1895 April 25; Aug. 1; Dec. 29, 4 ALS (Box 29)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Ellie Miles 1895 April 27, ALS (Box 29)
- Margaret J. Preston to Mary Stuart Smith 1895 May 13-Dec. 9, 2 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 29)
- M. S. DeVere to Professor Kent and Smith 1895 May-Dec., 10 ALS (Box 29)
- Thomas Fitzhugh to Charles W. Kent 1895 June 2, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1895 June 7 & July 17, 2 ALS (Box 29)
- Francis Harrison Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1895 June 21-Dec. 25, 4 ALS, 1 AL (Box 29)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1895 July-Dec., 19 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1895 Aug. 7-Sept. 24, 3 ALS (Box 29)
- Anne Ritchie to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1895 Aug. 22, ALS (Box 29)
- Danske Dandridge to Mary Stuart Smith [1895] Sept. 23, ALS (Box 29)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to cousin, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1895 Oct. 17, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary L. Magill to Charles W. Kent 1895 Oct. 17, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1895 Oct. 21-Dec. 9, 4 ALS (Box 29)
- James Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1895 Oct. 28, ALS (Box 29)
- Eldgerton S. Rodgers to Lt. John T. Knight 1895 Nov. 1, TLS (Box 29)
- Rosalie Bell to Mrs. Charles W. Kent 1895 Nov. 24 & 25, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith [1895 Dec. 10], 5 ALS (Box 29)
- T. H. Ellie to Professor C. W. Kent 1895 Dec. 11, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 Jan. 2-25, 5 ALS (Box 29)
- (Eliza) Carter Thornton to Uncle Francis H. Smith 1896 Jan. 5, ALS (Box 29)
- Eleanor Rosalie Harrison (Mrs. M. W. Thornton) to brother-in-law Francis H. Smith 1896 Jan. 6, ALS (Box 29)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith 1896 Jan. 20-Aug. 24, 2 ALS, 1 AL (Box 29)
- Margaret J. Preston to Mary Stuart Smith 1896 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 29)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1896 Jan.-June, 13 ALS, 7 TLS (Box 29)
- Edward B. Smith to Professor F. H. Smith, J. Howard Smith 1896 Feb. 27-Dec. 9, 3 ALS, 2 APCS (Box 29)
- Hunter, Pendleton to C. W. Kent 1896 March 2 & Aug. 21, 2 ALS (Box 29)
- Eleanor R. Harrison Thornton to sister, Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1896 March 5, ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 March 8-May 17, 4 ALS (Box 30)
- E. V. Valentine to Charles W. Kent 1896 April 1, ALS (Box 30)
- Rosalie Rives to Eleanor A. Smith 1896 April 27, ALS (Box 30)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 May 18-Nov. 9, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 June 14-July 7, 4 ALS (Box 30)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1896 June 15-July 9, 4 ALS, 1 AN (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1896 July 2-13, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- L. V. Turner to Charles W. Kent 1896 July 9, ALS (Box 30)
- Letters to C. W. Kent 1896 July-Dec., 17 ALS, 1 AL, 2 TLS, 1 AN (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1896 Aug. 11-30, 4 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, George Tucker Smith 1896 Aug. 16-29, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- F. H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Fielding Miles (later Mrs. C. W. Kent) 1896 Aug. 27, ALS (Box 30)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1896 Aug. 27, ALS (Box 30)
- M. Schele DeVere to Professor Kent 1896 Aug. 31, ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 Sept. 6-21, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son Dr. George Tucker Smith 1896 Oct. 5-Dec. 28, 8 ALS (Box 30)
- Woodrow Wilson to Francis H. Smith 1896 Oct. 13, TLS (Box 30)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1896 [Oct. 23]-Nov. 20, 4 ALS (Box 30)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1896 Nov. 11, ALS (Box 30)
- Professor Venable to Professor F. H. Smith 1896 Nov. 16, ALS (Box 30)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1897 Jan. 18 & 26, 2 ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart to husband, F. H. Smith 1897 Jan. 24 & Aug. 25, 2 ALS (Box 30)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1897 Jan.-June, 39 ALS, 9 TLS, 2 APCS 1 Telegram (Box 30)
- Professor Venable to Professor Kent 1897 Feb. 12, ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 Feb. 16-June 13, 7 ALS (Box 30)
- Bennett Windue to Charles W. Kent 1897 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 30)
- Henry William Harrison to Dr. Kent 1897 Feb. 27, ALS (Box 30)
- John Singleton Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1897 March 17, ALS (Box 30)
- Danske Dandridge to [Mary Stuart Smith] 1897 March, ALS (Box 30)
- Margaret J. Preston to Mary Stuart Smith 1897 April 13, AL (Box 30)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1897 April 21, ALS (Box 30)
- Mary L. Magill to J. F. McLaughlin 1897 April 27, ALS (Box 30)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1897 May 11 & Aug. 5, 2 ALS (Box 30)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 May 31-Aug. 11, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- James. M. Garnett to Professor F. H. Smith 1897 June 15, ALS (Box 30)
- William M. Thornton to C. W. Kent 1897 July 2, ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 July 5-Aug. 23, 8 ALS (Box 30)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1897 July-Dec., 36 ALS, 2 TLS, 2 APCS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 Aug. 26-Oct. 4, 7 ALS (Box 30)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1897 Sept. 13, ALS (Box 30)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 Oct. 1-10, 3 ALS (Box 30)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 Oct. 18-Nov. 16, 5 ALS (Box 31)
- Bennett Windue to Charles W. Kent 1897 Oct. 25, ALS (Box 31)
- W. Gordon McCabe to C. W. Kent 1897 Oct. 27, ALS (Box 31)
- Hunter Pendleton to C. W. Kent 1897 Oct. 30, ALS (Box 31)
- John M. Manly to C. W. Kent 1897 Nov. 1, ALS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1897 Nov. 23-Dec. 20, 5 ALS (Box 31)
- Correspondence to C. W. Kent 1898 Jan. 28-May 20, 1 ALS, 3 TLS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 Jan. 31-Feb. 8, 4 ALS (Box 31)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1898 Jan.-June, 49 ALS, 11 TLS, 3 TL, 3 APCS (Box 31)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1898 Feb. 6, ALS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 Feb. 11-March 7, 5 ALS (Box 31)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1898 Feb. 16, ALS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 March 14-April 4, 5 ALS (Box 31)
- Professor Venable to Professor Kent 1898 March 24-Oct. 1, 2 ALS (Box 31)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1898 March 30, TLS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 April 15-July 8, 6 ALS (Box 31)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1898 April 22, TLS (Box 31)
- Hunter Pendleton to C. W. Kent 1898 June 2, ALS (Box 31)
- F. H. Smith to wife, M. S. Smith 1898 June 20, ALS (Box 31)
- Letters to Francis H. Smith 1898 June-July, 3 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 31)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 July 7-Aug. 30, 2 ALS (Box 31)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1898 July 11-Dec. 5, 6 ALS (Box 31)
- James P. C. Southall to Francis P. C. Smith 1898 July 16, ALS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to daughter, Mary Stuart Smith 1898 July 18, 30, & Aug. 4, 2 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 31)
- Francis H. Smith to Duncan Smith 1898 July 21, 2 ALS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to son, (James) Duncan Smith 1898 July 21, ALS (Box 31)
- James P. C. Southall to Francis H. Smith 1898 July 22, ALS (Box 31)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1898 July-Dec., 38 ALS, 15 TLS (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 Aug. 1-Sept. 13, 5 ALS (Box 31)
- Rosalie Smith to George Tucker Smith 1898 Aug. 30, ALS (Box 31)
- Netta Jones to Francis H. Smith 1898 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 31)
- Invitation to Reunion of 43rd Battalion Virginia Cavalry-Mosby's Men 1898 Oct. 5, ALS, and Printed Invitation (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1898 Oct. 6-Dec. 26, 6 ALS (Box 31)
- Thomas Nelson Page to Charles W. Kent 1898 Nov. 27, ALS (Box 31)
- R. T. Irvine to C. W. Kent 1898 Dec. 22, TLS (Box 31)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith, (sister) 1898 Dec. 26, ALS (Box 31)
- Letters re: Purchase of Library of George F. Holmes 1898-1899, 10 ALS, 13 TLS, 4 TL (Box 31)
- Invitation for ceremonies connected with new buildings - University of Virginia 1898, Printed invitation (Box 31)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Jan. 11-Feb. 13, 6 ALS (Box 32)
- Francis H. Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Jan. 14 & July 31, 5 ALS (Box 32)
- John B. Table to Charles W. Kent 1899 Jan. 16, ALS (Box 32)
- Correspondence of Charles W. Kent 1899 Jan.-June, 58 ALS, 12 TLS, 2 Printed Invitations (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 March 6-April 17, 6 ALS (Box 32)
- W. Gordon McCabe to C. W. Kent 1899 March 27, ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1899 April 5-June 30, 3 ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 May 1-24, 6 ALS (Box 32)
- Williette (Stevens) Baughman to aunt, Mary Jane Harrison 1899 May 2, ALS (Box 32)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Mary Stuart Harrison 1899 June 1, ALS (Box 32)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1899 June 7, TLS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 189 June 7-26, 4 ALS (Box 32)
- G. W. Cobb to Charles W. Kent 1899 June 8, ALS (Box 32)
- Mary S. Smith to Dr. George T. Smith [1899 June 21], ALS (Box 32)
- Rosalie Bell to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1899 June 27, ALS (Box 32)
- Correspondence of C. W. Kent concerning J. R. Thompson 1899 June-Nov., 12 ALS, 1 AL, 2 TLS, 1 TL, 1 APCS, 2 Telegrams (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1899 July 1, ALS (Box 32)
- M. H. Van Nuys to Professor Francis H. Smith 1899 July 1, ALS (Box 32)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1899 July 3 & 7, 4 ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1899 July 3-10, 5 ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 July 3-27, 3 ALS (Box 32)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1899 July 8-18, 6 ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1899 July 11-14, 3 ALS (Box 32)
- Hunter Pendleton to C. W. Kent 1899 June 12, ALS (Box 32)
- G. Washington Ball to James T. White & Co. 1899 July 15, ALS (Box 32)
- P. B. Barringer and O. Stowe to Professor F. H. Smith 1899 July 21 & 24, 1 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1899 July 26-29, 5 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 32)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1899 July 30, ALS (Box 32)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1899 July-Dec., 34 ALS, 15 TLS, 1 APCS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Aug. 4-23, 5 ALS (Box 32)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1899 Aug. 5-Sept. 10, 4 ALS (Box 32)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mary Stuart Smith 1899 [Aug. 9] & Sept. 2, 2 ALS (Box 32)
- F. H. Smith to duaghter, Mrs. C. W. Kent 1899 Sept. 2, ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Sept. 5-27, 5 ALS (Box 32)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Oct. 2-30, 5 ALS (Box 33)
- Theodore Wong to C. W. Kent 1899 Nov. 22, ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to George Tucker Smith [ ca. 1899] Dec. 1, 2 ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1899 Dec. 2-25, 4 ALS (Box 33)
- Minnie L. Harrison (Mrs. M. White Williamson) to cousin, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1899 Dec. 23, ALS (Box 33)
- R. Taylor to Professors C. W. Kent 1899 Dec. 31, TLS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to son, James Duncan Smith 1899 Dec., ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1900 Jan. 2-30, 4 ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1900 Feb. 12-27, 3 ALS (Box 33)
- Mannassas Journal B. F. Johnson Publishing Co. to C. W. Kent 1900 Feb. 18 & April 28, ALS and TLS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1900 March 6 & March 25, 4 ALS (Box 33)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1900 March 14 & 15, 2 ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1900 March 16-Sept. 5, 2 ALS (Box 33)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1900 March 17, ALS (Box 33)
- [?] to Mrs. Smith 1900 March 26, (fragment) (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1900 April 2-24, 5 ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1900 May 22-June 11, 3 ALS (Box 33)
- Hamilton W. Mabin to Mrs. Charles Kent 1900 May 26, ALS (Box 33)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Fielding D. Miles 1900 Aug. 17, ALS (Box 33)
- "Uncle Saint" to Mary Stewart Smith 1900 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 33)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1900 Oct. 15, ALS (Box 33)
- M. J. Calhoun to [?] 1900 Oct. 29, ALS (Box 33)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1900, 33 ALS, 22 TLS, 1 printed invitation (Box 33)
- James Duncan Smith to mother, Mary Stuart Smith 1901 April 6, ALS (Box 33)
- John Hunter, Jr. to C. W. Kent 1901 April 8, 2 ALS (Box 33)
- B. C. Gildersleeve to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1901 April 15, ALS (Box 33)
- E. E. White to C. W. Kent 1901 April 19, ALS (Box 33)
- B. Matthews to Charles W. Kent 1901 April 22, ALS (Box 33)
- George Dunlop to C. W. Kent 1901 May 3, ALS (Box 33)
- Marie Duncan Harrison to sister-in-law, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1901 May 7, ALS (Box 33)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1901 June 22-Sept. 13, 5 ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1901 June 22-Sept. 24, 5 ALS (Box 33)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1901 June 23, ALS (Box 33)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1901 June 26, ALS (Box 33)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1901 June 30, ALS (Box 33)
- James R. C. Southall to Francis H. Smith 1901 July 2, ALS (Box 33)
- Willoughby Reade to C. W. Kent 1901 July 5, ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor Smith (Kent) 1901 July 12-Sept. 6, 3 ALS (Box 33)
- henry Van Dyke to C. W. Kent 1901 Aug. 8, ALS (Box 33)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1901 Sept. 8-14, 6 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 33)
- Alfred V. Thom to Francis H. Smith 1901 Sept. 10, TLS (Box 33)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1901 Nov. 19, ALS (Box 33)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1901, 42 ALS, 26 TLS (Box 33)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1902 Feb. 3, TLS (Box 34)
- James Grant Wilson to B. B. Minor 1902 Feb. 28, ALS (Box 34)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith, [sister] 1902 March 10, ALS (Box 34)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1902 March 31 & April 5, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- T. H. Cary and G. R. Coler to C. W. Kent 1902 April 11 & Sept. 9, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- M. W. Humphreys to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1902 June 22, ALS (Box 34)
- H. W. Mabie to Professor C. W. Kent 1902 July 18, TLS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1902 Aug. 5-14, 5 ALS (Box 34)
- John L. Willims to Francis H. Smith 1902 Aug. 5 & Nov. 18, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Thomas H. Carter to Professor F. H. Smith 1902 Aug. 6, ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith (Kent) 1902 Aug. 9 & Sept. 15, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1902 Aug. 21, ALS (Box 34)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor Smith Kent 1902 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 34)
- John S. Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1902 Sept. 4, ALS (Box 34)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1902 Oct. 27, TLS (Box 34)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to Mrs. Charles Kent 1902 Nov. 3, ALS (Box 34)
- Correspondence Chaplin Committee (University of Virginia) 1902, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1902, 33 ALS, 9 TLS (Box 34)
- E. A. Alderman to Professor C. W. Kent 193 Jan. 27 & April 2, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith (Kent) 1903 Feb. 13, ALS (Box 34)
- F. H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor S. Kent 1903 Feb. 20, ALS (Box 34)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1903 March 21-June 27, 5 ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor Smith (Kent) 1903 April 15-May 11, 6 ALS (Box 34)
- John S. Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1903 June 19 & Sept. 9, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1903 June 30-Dec. 22, 4 ALS (Box 34)
- M. Sheffey Latane to Mary Stuart Smith 1903 Aug. [29], ALS (Box 34)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1903, 4 ALS, 5 TLS (Box 34)
- F. H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor S. Kent 1904 Jan. 2-Sept. 5, 3 ALS (Box 34)
- H. A. Kelly to C. W. Kent, A. C. Gordon 1904 Feb. 2 & June 20, 2 ALS (Box 34)